const quiz2data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "conditionals 2",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "blue", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "red", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "Hello, this is my new website."
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "If he ___ hard, he ___ the exam.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "will study / will pass", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "studies / will pass", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "When there is a real possibility that this condition will happen we use first conditional. The structure is:  ",
      help1: "if + present simple , will + infinitive"
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "If you heat water to 100Â°C, it ___",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "boils", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "will boil", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use Zero Conditional when we talk about a general truth, like a scientific fact. The result of the condition is an absolute certainty. The structure is: ",
      help1: " if + present simple, present simple"
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: ""
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "If you ___, you ____ fulfill your dreams.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "didn't try / won't", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "don't try / will not", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "When there is a real possibility that this condition will happen we use first conditional. The structure is:  ",
      help1: "if + present simple , will + infinitive"
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: ""
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: ""
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "If I get the job, I ___ move to London.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "will ", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "would", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "When there is a real possibility that this condition will happen we use first conditional. The structure is:  ",
      help1: "if + present simple , will + infinitive"
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: ""
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "Spiders ___ when they ___ threaten.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "bite / are", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "bites / will be", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use Zero Conditional when the result of the condition is always true. It's a fact. Notice that sometimes we can use 'when' instead of 'if'. The structure is: ",
      help1: " if + present simple, present simple"
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "It ___ cheaper if we buy tickets online.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "would be", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "will be", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "When there is a real possibility that this condition will happen we use first conditional. The structure is:  ",
      help1: "if + present simple , will + infinitive"
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: ""
    },
    
]

export default quiz2data